(Penny:)We're not in a rush.
(Penny:)We'll set a date when
the time is right.
(Mrs Cooper:)It doesn't matter, sweetie.
(Mrs Cooper:)The moment a man lays
with a woman,
(Mrs Cooper:)they are married
in the eyes of the Lord.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Uch.
"Uch"?
The bible is "uch" to you?
(Dr Hofstadter:)No, I'm sorry.
(Dr Hofstadter:)That was inappropriate.
(Dr Hofstadter:)As a psychiatrist,
I know how important
(Dr Hofstadter:)people's superstitions
can be to them.
(Mrs Cooper:)You want to talk
about superstitions?
(Mrs Cooper:)Sheldon sent me
the books you wrote--
(Mrs Cooper:)all that nonsense
about superegos and ids.
(Mrs Cooper:)What bull dropped that
on the barn floor?
(Dr Hofstadter:)His name is Sigmund Freud.
Hey, look at that!
(Penny:)You both believe in
Jewish bearded guys.
(Mrs Cooper:)Stay out of this.
(Penny:)Mm-hmm.
(Mrs Cooper:)At least the bearded man
that I believe in
(Mrs Cooper:)preaches love and compassion.
(Mrs Cooper:)All yours
talks about is
(Mrs Cooper:)why you hold in your poop
(Mrs Cooper:)and want to crawl back
inside your mama.